{
    "id": "bacdbba1c8914c2b80706e1f0da1ccd6",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "All the members of the family have a rightful claim to the ...................... property.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ancient",
                "ancestral",
                "ancestry"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "007cb9ab46f0428daedfad9ee6e61d3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The vehicle was badly damaged but the driver escaped .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "miracle",
                "miraculous",
                "miraculously"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "025cb190b1e54ca88cbab79a7c1cf349"
        },
        {
            "question": "The village woman looked at the crowds and the traffic in .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bewilder",
                "bewilderment",
                "bewildered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cca591045c5f4518a1033fea1869bf8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I visit Canada .....................… to meet my sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "occasional",
                "occasionally"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0258511071704eda9c6869ba8f6deb2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister gave a …………………. reply to his detractors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "befit",
                "befitted",
                "befitting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a541969025343679dc6f602e7bf227e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nehru’s ………………….. with Gandhi helped him change his views.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "associate",
                "associative",
                "association"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4eb1511c44be47c08c095901baab8ac3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Great leaders ..................... people even after they are gone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inspire",
                "inspiration",
                "inspirational"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db801b9442494b418e8e65c19bf2a7f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think there is any ………………… for you to come again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "necessary",
                "necessity",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6ba2f2e14064a638548bf56aa479c59"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was very ....................... about the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthusiasm",
                "enthusiastic",
                "enthusiastically"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7ead03e0d6d42fe9d3ae5dd57d3980f"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ....................... with politics affected his career.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preoccupy",
                "preoccupation",
                "preoccupational"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7af2d83bc244a06ba529fdfe3e009fa"
        }
    ]
}